plusvitality.com 2019-02-16

# Privacy + PlusVitality

PlusVitality respects your right to privacy. All “personal information” collected by PlusVitality through this Site, such as name, title, company name, address, telephone number, and/or e-mail address that you voluntarily provide through this Site or by e-mail correspondence will be used by PlusVitality to contact you regarding your inquiries and to supply you with requested information regarding PlusVitality’s products and services.

PlusVitality and/or its affiliates may use personal information and monitor website activity generally, to collect information on how this Site is used and the volume and frequecy of access so that we may improve this Site , as well as PlusVitality’s related services. PlusVitality will not provide your information to unrelated third parties without your prior express consent, except as permitted under this Privacy Policy.

PlusVitality may also use temporary “cookies” which is data sent to your web browser and stored on your computer. These cookies permit our server to identify you when you visit the Site in the future. Most web browsers will allow you to be notified if a cookie is sent to you to enable you to decide if you want to accept it or not. Please be aware that if cookies are disabled on your computer, some features/functions of this Site may not work properly.

PlusVitality will co-operate with the governmental authorities and comply with all court orders involving requests for personal information.

The personal information PlusVitality collects on this Site is an asset of PlusVitality‘s business and in the event that PlusVitality, or substantially all of its assets, are acquitted or become the subject of a merger, such information may be transferred.

Please contact PlusVitality if you have any questions concerning PlusVitality’s privacy policy, the way PlusVitality uses your personal information or if you would like to review your personal information that Smith’s has collected in order to update or delete it from our system.

This privacy policy applies to information collected over this Site. PlusVitality reserves the right to apply different policies to information collected off-line.
